Well, gentlemen,
Well, 先生们,
how can I help you today?
今天我能为你们做些什么?
We're just looking, thanks.
我们只是看看, 谢谢.
Very good, very good.
很好, 很好.
Let me ask you a question.
让我问你一个问题.
Are you interested in glamour?
你是对引人注目的外表(glamour)感兴趣呢?
Or reliability?
还是对可靠性感兴趣?
I'm interested in a car.
我对汽车感兴趣.
Very good.
很好.
What can you tell us about this one?
你能向我们介绍一下这辆车吗?
She's a beauty, isn't she? An 82.
她简直是位美人儿, 是不是? 1982年的.
Was it always this color?
它一直是这个颜色吗?
How many miles on it?
它跑了多少英里了?
162, 000 happy miles. And many more to go, I'm sure.
顺顺当当地跑了16万2千英里. 还可以跑许多英里, 我敢保证.
Was there only one owner?
以前它只有一个车主吗?
Ah, no. Several owners. Several very happy owners.
Ah,no. 有过几个了. 几个十分满意的主人.
How often has it been serviced?
它多长时间维修一次?
You know, the funny thing is,
你知道, 有趣的事情是,
this car ran so well, it hardly ever got serviced.
这车跑得非常好, 它几乎从未维修过.
Except after one or two collisions.
除了一两次撞车后.
Isn't that remarkable?
是不是很棒?
I don't understand.
我不明白.
How could the owners ever give it up?
那些车主怎么会不要它了?
Trade-in. They were moving up.
以旧换新嘛. 他们都升级了.
Just like you Kevin. Moving up.
就像你一样, Kevin. 也升级了.